Attention all units... HQ calling Central Patrol.
各挝蛔⒁狻部呼叫中^警
A Chinese male robber is holding a hostage on Dudell street.
有一名男子在中h
All units proceed immediately.
各挝涣⒓磁扇说浆F鲋г
Don't come over. I'll kill him.
不要^恚^砦揖⒘怂
Don't come over.
yy不要^恚不要^
Two guards are dead.
S警官，擅\nT被打死了
Shit, so many of us and we can't do anything.
阿金，一人都搞不定，@NC囊
We'll be the laughing stock of town.
什N咚咚，他有人|
Let him go.
他走
Just like that case of the jeweller's.
照上次表店那件案子做
That hostage was seriously injured.
那人|倒霉了
He got away and the hostage was still hurt.
他跑掉，我才倒霉
Same deal, the hostage is yours, I get the nutcase.
戆桑人|你的，子是我的
You guys will let him go.
你@群桶，早晚都人家跑掉
Get over there.
不快L到一去
- Dare you shoot? - Put your gun down.
有N你就_  把放下
You guys never put on a good show.
你]有成功^
Put your gun down, get over there.
不快把放下
Kam, take a look at the hostage.
阿金，^去看看人|怎N恿耍
You bastards, shooting at the hostage!
帜隳铮_打人|
I'll sue you.
我要告你祖宗十八代
Why don't you send me to the hospital?
不送我上t院去？
The hostage asked me why I shot him.
才那人|我槭颤N要_打他
I told him the gun misfired.
我跟他f，我支走火了
He says he'll sue.
他f，他要告我了
These guns are supplied by the U.K.
我跟他v，是英人o我的
Go sue the England.
要告就去告那些英佬
- And he started crying. - Kam.
然後他就哭了  阿金
You go ahead first.
我有c事，你先回去
The boss wants to see us. Let's take his lecture together.
上要找我，要挨R一起挨R
What a mess!
什N咚咚
Your spinal nerves are affecting your right hand.
是你的脊椎神影了你的右手
Making it periodically out of control.
所以引起你g歇性的o法控制
This is very serious.
@邮呛芪ｋU的
Before it gets worse,
在病情夯之前
you should get a suspension first.
你最好先申r停
"Malaysia"
（R砦）
"HANG FUNG SHIPPING CO. LTD."
（aS船沼邢薰司）
Mr. Tse? I've been looking for you.
x先生是幔课找你好久了
One of my staff left something at the hotel.
我的同事不小心在酒店e掉了包|西
You've got it, right? Please return it.
f你斓搅耍你o我
Yes, the photo album.
就是@本相簿
You must have seen the shipping schedule,
你一定看到了那船期表
and went to check us out at the Shipping Company.
所以@商斓酱展司碚{查我
The guy is too greedy.
@人失≡谔心
I don't care where he's from, kill him.
不管他是哪l道上的，值羲
Yes!
是
Petrol.
C油
Send him on his way.
送他一程
The body is over there.
企w在那
- What have you found? - A bag and a HK passport.
有什NlF  有皮包及香港o照
Inform the HK Police immediately.
快通知香港警方
"Hong Kong".
（香港）
"Resignation"
（o）
"SUPERINTENDENT MR. MCDONALD"
（SUPERlNTENDENTMR.MCDONALD）
Come in.
M
You remember your old partner, Skinny Tse.
得你以前拍n毛x，x璋？
He may have been killed in Malaysia.
他最近岩稍隈R砦被人⑺懒
The body will be back tomorrow.
企w明天\回
You were such friends with him.
我知道你和阿x情同手足
You'd want to do the case anyway, right?
@宗案子就算我不找你
Freeze, Police!
e樱警察
Be care!
小心
"Work carefully and safely"
（小心工作，安全第一）
Informer!
奸
All of you stay back.
yy_
Don't move, get back to the station.
e樱抓回局e去
Are you alright?
阿x…你]事吧？
- My leg. - Tse, brace up.
_  阿x，你要振作c
John.
S邦
Two more weeks to the wedding.
我有Y拜就Y婚了
Are you regretting it?
你後悔？
The wedding has to be postponed.
莉，婚Y要延tc
Why?
延t？槭颤N？
Before it gets worse.
在病情夯之前
You better apply for suspension first.
你最好先申r停
I have my reasons.
莉，我有苦衷的
I've taken on Tse's case.
我接了阿x那宗案子做
It's best if we wait until the case is over.
我最好等@宗案子k完了才面
Let me take you home.
我送你回去
"Malaysia"
（R砦）
Tse looks pretty good all dressed up.
看睚毛x穿起警察制服
Quite smart.
都子⒚魃裎
Looks as if he could live to 90.
好像九十q都不死的
Then pop, he's gone.
想不到@N颍@N年p就死了
Hope it's not him.
希望那l撇皇撬
The loose ends from the drug case may have caused his murder.
不是因樯洗文亲诙酒钒赣嘘P
He was followed to Malaysia.
被人跟到大R才⑺浪吧
Of course not. His boss was killed in jail.
然不是，他的老大
Tse hid in S.E. Asia cause he wanted out.
阿x避去|南，就是想洗手不
My negligence forced Tse to go into hiding.
那次要不是我疏忽
Sergeant Lan, I'm Waipong Wong.
{ML，我是SS邦
Call this rookie 1006 Kwok Keung Lun.
同我Call一新人1006
Tell him to meet me at the morgue.
叫他去房找我
I'm Pak, not Lan.
SSir，我不是{ML，我是白ML
Sergeant Lan has gone on leave.
{ML同洪Sir去了度假
I'll call the rookie for you.
我同你Call那新人了
Got a call.
有人Call我
- You want to squash me to death? - Sorry!
你想A死我？  Σ黄
Back...
退後…
Nurse, is it serious?
o士，那位小姐的不很乐兀
Over 10 stitches. Won't be able to sit for a while.
p了十揍了，有一段日子不能坐
A permanent scar too.
那即是永h留下
Please call me if there are any changes.
她有什N事你Call我
I'm from the Police. My name is...
我是警察，我名…
And you're Ada?
你叫艾_？
This is my number.
@是我
Call me if something happens.
她有什N事，你得Call我
Call me even if nothing happens.
]事也可以Call我，得Call我
Shit, forgot to call back.
糗了，忘了回Call了
Inspector Ong from Malaysia.
S警官，大R翁督察砹
- Our Inspector Wong. - Welcome!
@就是S警官  g迎
Crime Unit, Chief Inspector Waipong Wong.
刑事M督察，SS邦
I'm Chat Fu Ong.
我是翁振富
Just call me John.
叫我S邦
And me, Ong.
叫我阿翁
Come inside.
M
Sorry!
Σ黄
Do you know Chief Inspector Wong?
你J不JRSS邦督察
Is he here? He told me to report here.
他Call我蟮降
I'm 1006, Kwok Keung Lun.
我是1006，
Shit!
什N咚咚
Let's begin.
各位，我_始了
- I'm Kam! - How are you!
我叫阿金  你好
Since Malaysia has notified us.
自拇篑R通知了我@
We've contacted Tse's family.
我也j^阿x的家人跟H戚
He's been missing for 2 weeks.
C他失了半月
If Tse's case involves both areas,
如果阿x@件案子涉及地方
we'll probably have to go to Malaysia.
我就要到大R去
- Your turn, Ong. - Good.
翁警官，你了  好
Run it!
放
The deceased was 1.7m,
那企w，身高大s170公分
estimated weight 45kg.
w重估45公斤
Was burnt with petrol.
被人用汽油^
Bruises on his bones.
身上骨骼被重物撞暨^
But basically the body is in one piece.
不^企w算四肢R全
X-ray shows his left leg has been operated on,
X光片@示他的左_，曾舆^手g
where a metal joint was put in.
所以小腿部分有一根z
It matches completely with your X-rays.
同你提供姓x的X光片，完全吻合
We found his bag at the scene of murder.
手提袋是我在F龈浇找到的
With a photocopy of shipping schedules.
e面有一影印的船期表
Those circled are ships bounds for Hong Kong.
@些都是硐愀鄣拇
These duplicated photo were also in the bag.
有@些翻照的照片
Do you recognize?
也是在手提袋e找到的，J不JR
You won't get sick over this.
看到@就不吐了吧
The mousetachio is Kanin Ho.
照片e那小E子叫R家年
He owns a shipping Company.
是香港一家船展司的老
He was obviously blackmailed.
@些照片很明@是用砝账魉的
As for Tse' murder,
有P姓x的死因，唯一的索
the only clue lies with him.
就在他身上
But investigating rich men is a problem.
不^要查有X人是很麻
See if you have enough clout.
要看你手段虿蚋呙
John!
S邦
The guy with Ho is from Malaysia.
同R家年一R的那人是拇篑R淼
Do you know him?
你J不JR？
He is Ching Han, doing very well in Hong Kong lately.
他叫n政，最近在香港混得不e
He's something, got filthy rich just like that.
U有本事，一下子就l起砹
Can't imagine he has a clean record.
看他的底子，也不乾Q到哪e去
What are you up to now, Clumsy Lun.
搞什N咚咚？
Self-made bugging device.
`器
Doesn't work. No sound.
你娘，有]有到的
Maybe the batteries are flat?
可能池]了吧
You're using batteries!
池？F在用池？
It's the age of hydro-electricity.
人家F在已把水b在手lel了
You just have to spit on it and it works.
你用那N吐吐口水就可以用的
- Have you tried the ones you piss on. - Kam.
有那N用尿的  阿金
You with him go away!
你跟小弟^去
I'm going with the rookie to check Ho out.
看看能不能得幽姓R的？
We're C.I.D. From Central Crime Unit.
中^刑事M警T
We would like Mr. Ho to assist in an investigation.
我想R先生到警局忙
What do you mean by this?
大庭V，你想质颤N？
Make an appointment with my office.
到我k公室As吧
Should I take a gift too?
要不要ФY物？
I'm not kidding you.
我不是跟你_玩笑
Talk to my lawyer.
有什N事找我律
He's stalling.
]有k法，他不甩我
Kam, can you see over there by the flag poles.
阿金，有]有看到旗U那
Someone's taking pictures of us.
有人拿著相Cχ我
Shit, must be a talent scout.
不是星探？
- There's another there on the podium. - Kam, Lun.
平台也有一  阿金、阿
You fix the one at the flag poles.
你去Ω镀U那人
They've planned their exit.
被跑掉了
I though only cops tailed people.
我以槲是矶⑷说
How come we're being tailed?
怎N反被人家盯上呢？
Sign here please.
莉，你一下
Sorry, it's urgent.
s著用的，不好意思
- Thanks! - Crime Unit!
xx  刑事M
Is Inspector Wong there?
SS邦督察在幔
Hold on.
等一等
Waipong Wong!
SS邦
John, it's me, Maggie.
S邦，我是莉
I told you we stop meeting each other for a while.
我跟你f^r不要面
Don't call again.
你不要再打
John!
S邦…
We've got the gay kid who's with Ho.
S警官，我已找到那同性倭
His name is Ah Chi. Lives in Wanchai, comes out rarely.
他叫做阿志就住在匙校很少出砘
Only wholesale deals, no retail trade.
他通常只做包月的，不做召
Been to every gay hangout and 2 guys know him.
全香港玻璃圈只有人JR他
- Bring him in. - Yes!
R上找他^  是
I'm Inspector Wong from Crime Unit.
我是刑事M督察SS邦
We have an appointment with Mr. Ho at 4 p.m.
我s了R先生四c
Do you have a booking?
你根本就]有As
How can you say there's no appointment!
你怎N可以f我]有As
I came personally yesterday.
我昨天H自上淼
Mr. Ho is busy for the rest of the month.
R先生@半月都]有rg你
Open up.
_T
So noisy, must be a gay party.
_玻璃大是不是？
Shit.
搞什N咚咚？
Is John there?
SS邦在幔
What? Go on.
我是，阿翁，你f吧
The circled ship is arriving today and will leave in 2 days' time.
船期表打了圈的那艘船，今天到香港
Do we have time to apply for a permit.
有]有rg拿搜查令？
It's too big, we won't have time to search.
船@N大，就算拿到也聿患安榱
We'll discuss it when I get back.
好，我回碓僬f
The guy's still following.
他的，太q^上油粒
I know I've failed.
S警官，我也知道自己很d
Tried twice to meet the guy.
s了纱味技s不到那砘
I didn't mean you.
我不是f你
I meant those guys are tailing us again.
我是f那群跟屁x又出F了
Tailing us?
跟屁x？
- If send up here. - Where?
既然送上T  在哪e？
Let's play hide and seek.
就跟他玩捉迷藏吧
Don't scare them.
不要跑他
You take one end, I'll take the other.
我z一人一逮住他
Go!
去
Careful!
小心c
Freeze, C.I. D!
不要樱警察
Gun, he's got a gun.
，他有
Move off.
小心
Freeze.
不要
You've got guns too. You can shoot too!
你也有，不_？
Hell.
…
You're lucky to be alive.
@次算你命大，把命o旎砹
Are you alright? Scared the hell out of me.
孩子你]事吧？死了
Well, Sir?
S警官，怎N樱
What about the one you were after?
你追的人呢？
- He got away. - O. K?
跑了  你]事吧？
Fine.
]事
- Fix them up. - Yes, sir!
找人硖理一下  是，警官
Shit! Two are gone in a day.
的，一天e就死了
Looks like a really tricky case.
看磉@案子不
They really want to know where we're going.
Ψ揭蚕胫道我的行
Ho is leaving for Seattle tomorrow.
姓R的明晚去西雅D
What can we do if he leaves?
他一走怎N查？
We can't stop him from going.
我]有嗔ψ柚顾
But I can fix it so that he can't go.
不^我可以他去不成
Kam, let's put on a good show tomorrow.
阿金，我明天跟他做
We'll have some fun with him.
搞到他翻橹
Good, it won't so boring then.
他是什N咚咚，@[蚝猛
What we do to Ho tomorrow is not in the rule book.
明天我用的方法，超越常
Can lose your job anytime.
Sr都可能被_除
If you don't want to take part.
如果你不想⒓
I'll apply for your transfer.
可以{M
I'm right behind you.
S警官，我是砀你W的
I can't transfer just after I've started.
]道理一砭捅徽{走
We'll have some fun!
我要跟你同M退
You got my photos to coerce me into co-operation.
你拍了我的照片
Now there's murder and you hang in on me?
F在出了人命，又想拖我下水
Who did you kill in Malaysia?
在大R⑺赖哪人到底是l？
Why are the cops after me?
槭颤N警察找上我？
I've got someone tailing the cops.
，我已派人盯住那些警察
Anything happens, I'll handle it.
有什N屿o，我付
The guy was killed in Malaysia,
在大R⑺赖哪人
so that your photos won't get out.
不是榱伺履隳切
Your other Board Members will not like it.
你是准夜司的董事
If this is revealed.
曝露出
Your companies will suffer.
船展司跟y行信u都受影
You know I can fix the cops and the gangs.
你知道，黑白傻牢叶颊值米
If you're smart, wait for the cargo to arrive safely,
明的，就等那些D了手
or else I can squash you with my little finger.
否t我用小指^都可以核滥
You hear?
到了]有？
Don't come looking for me.
@滋欤你不用碚椅
I'll arrange everything for you.
你的事我o你安排好
Someone will meet you in Seattle.
西雅D那有人斫幽愕
I'm Lun from Crime Unit.
我是刑事M
Mr. Ho, lower your window please.
麻┠惆汛u下
Ignore him, go on.
e理他，走
Mr. Ho!
R先生…
He really ignored me.
S警官，那混蛋真的不理我
Forget it, we'll move in on him.
不理就α耍我F在要他好看
Kam, all yours.
阿金，你了
Got it.
知道了，S警官
Get going. You're really slow.
搞什N咚咚？反那N慢，_了
Slow? I haven't seen him yet.
慢，]看他了
Mr. Ho. It's a red light.
R先生，t
Just go on.
不管它，照走
You see that! Aren't you slow? Go over!
不承J反慢，追了
Are you crazy? We said punch twice.
你娘，打扇就好了
Get going, you're slow even to get away.
快逃了，他的
Where are the car keys?
匙呢？
Wait for me.
等等我
Shit, wait for me! You never told me about switching cars.
搞什N，等等我，Q也不跟我v
Who told you to drive this car away?
l叫你_@的？
We drive it away, he can't move.
把他_走，他就硬涣
Why didn't you say so before?
什N咚咚？我被他放子
If I didn't get on, I'd be in real trouble.
@硬皇撬赖煤茈y看
You're so fast, you're bound to catch me.
你反那N快，一定淼眉暗
You're putting me on.
你是故意的是不是？
Park it, I'll sort it out with you.
找地方翁袅耍停…
Mr. Ho, what happened?
R先生，l生什N事？
I don't know.
不知道？
Those guys were here to beat you up.
才他是存心碚夷愕
They'll probably come back.
Srl生第二次
You'd better give me a statement.
你是跟我回去口供吧
You are very brave. I'll sort it out with you.
你量很好，我翁
No one must know we're having it out.
不管llA，都不要v出去
I don't think you can take it. I'll let you start.
我看你是打不^我，你先出手
You go first. Cari mati.
「砣fA」
What "Cari mati", what do you mean?
什N「fA」，什N意思
It's Malay, you want to die, Curry what?
西班牙，跟你做哿
Carry me?
你R我是不是？
You started it.
你玩真的？
I let you go first.
打我弟弟
Cari mati!
我的
- Carry me... - My glasses...
你的眼R  我…
Your reaction is pretty fast too.
你反真的快
Hurry, we're not through yet. Cari mati!
然快，你娘的「fA」
Mr. Ho, look again. Do you recognize this man?
你看清楚，到底J不JR@人？
They were masked.
那人是檬著的
How would I know?
我怎N知道是不是他
No! Have you seen him before?
不知道，那你有]有^他？
No!
]有
Do you know who Skinny Tse is?
那你有]有^
Think clearly.
你再想清楚一c
I don't understand the law. Talk to my lawyer.
我不太懂法律
I'm going abroad tonight.
我晚上要出
Thank you for letting me return to the office.
我F在要回k公室去_
Sign the statement please.
R先生，你在口供上字
You may go.
你可以走了
I know how to look after people who do not know law.
我很照那些不懂法律的人
Thank you for your co-operation.
xx合作
We'll find your car.
你不用心，我M快把你找回
We've sent the stuff out.
S警官，|西已派人送去了
- Let's see how he reacts. - Yes!
去看看他的反  是
Please deliver this to Mr. Ho immediately.
麻┠憬唤oR先生
It's urgent. He must see it at once.
非常重要，他R上看
The meeting is adjourned.
各位，今天h到此，下次再f
He took the photos and returned to his office.
他拿了那些照片，回到自己k公室
I told him to take $1M to the cinema tomorrow.
我叫他下午五c
Will he take the bait?
他不上？
If he is behind Tse's killing.
如果他是阿x的主事者
He's going to murder this blackmailer as well.
一定也值暨@次勒索他的人
If he calls the police.
S警官，f一他蟀
Our plan fails.
那我@次不就失×耍
Nobody knows we're behind this.
不，]有人知道那封信是我搞的
If he does, we'll just take over the case.
如果他蟀福我就接下硖理
He's gone downstairs.
S警官，那姓R的下橇
Calling station, he's made a showing.
跹藕艚刑禊Z，姓R的上了
You go and play the blackmailer.
下午你假b那勒索的人
Wait for him in front of the cinema.
到蛟喝サ人
What if he recognizes me.
我怕他J出我
Get made up, then he won't.
找人o你化了y，他就J不出
Go and get prepared.
s快去浒
Kam, according to plans.
阿金，照M行
- Follow me. - Yes!
你跟我  是
Will you guys look out for me.
你要小心一c，看著我
No problem!
放心了
Calling grasshopper.
天Z呼叫小蚱蜢
What's it like at the cinema?
蛟耗沁情r如何？
We've been watching.
我@盯得很o
Lun has been waiting for over an hour.
隆咚I蹲在诟松
No show.
那姓R的到F在]出F
Nothing here either.
@e也]屿o
It's not time yet.
放心，r候]到，大家不要性急
Hey, one big blue whale went by.
正主出F了大家
- Everybody stand-by. - Yes!
快c  知道了
Climbing over at 6 furlong.
武大郎要跨诟肆
Bastard, you come right through the red lights!
你要死了，t裟氵…
You want to die young.
你才要死了
Can't you see me?
你把你B那N大，你委屈了
If you die, don't find me.
撞死了，不要找我
If you scratch me, I'll sue you.
撞死了我，非告你祖宗十八代不可
He's making a call.
S警官，姓R的在打
- Trace it. - Yes, Sir!
看他打哪e？  是，警官
Trace the call.
R上查清楚@l打哪e，Over
- Mr. Ching Han please! - Who is it?
叫n政  哪e找？
It's Ho! Tell him to come to the phone.
R家年，快c叫他
Mr. Han says you should not call him again.
n先生叫你以後不准再打o他
Han wouldn't take his call.
姓n的不接他
It's really you!
原碚娴氖悄
Something's up.
有r，上
- Don't move! - Don't shoot. She's my friend.
e 不要_，她是我女朋友
Abort. Abort. Everybody in positions.
`…大家回原位
Are you on duty? Then I won't get in the way.
你正在工作，那我不打_你了
Bye bye, careful! Bye bye.
ByeBye，小心c，ByeBye
Call me.
有空Call我
- Anything happening? - Nothing at all.
F在那情r怎恿耍  ]事了
Help! Come!
救命，快砣
Screaming for help!
有人喊救命
Go in!
有情r，立刻nM去
All units, move.
各挝涣⒖绦
Quick.
快
Call the police.
好可怕，死人了
You're foolish!
真tg，你
So slow.
反@N慢
What is it?
怎N回事？
The guy cut his wrists.
@砘锔钔笞
Oh shit!
搞什N咚咚？
- Get an ambulance. - Yes, Sir!
叫救o  是，警官
Get an ambulance.
小李，R上呼叫救o
He's still alive, get him to hospital.
]有死，快c送到t院去
- Hurry! - Quick.
好的  快
Call the Emergency ward to stand-by.
叫t院急救室
Notify P.C. Chan to seal all news.
通知警官封i一切消息
Don't let the reporters know.
不能蜃者知道
Also, tell Lun to wrap up.
有，通知阿收
You're out tomorrow.
你明天出院了
Still remember my name?
不得我叫什N名字？
- Ada. - Good boy.
艾_姐姐  乖
- Back home you can't jump. - OK.
回到家e可不要再蹦蹦跳跳的  好
Go see your female patient?
砜茨愕呐病人？
Today you scare me to death.
今天可真被你死了
I have a case at 15th floor.
我在十五怯案子
Tonight I'll be there all night.
今天整夜都在那e
Can I go there and find you?
可不可以上去找你？
OK, don't forget to bring some food.
行，e忘了宵夜
What kind of food?
什N宵夜？
Peanuts, chips, beef jerky, chocolates.
花生、酸梅、牛肉乾
That's junk food. I'll get you something else.
@些|西吃了]有IB
I bring something else for you.
我替你e的好了
O. K!
行
Ho is alright now.
R先生]有危U了
- He needs to rest, don't ask too long - Thanks.
他需要休息，e太久  xx
How's going inside?
e面怎N恿耍
If you were willing to co-operate,
R先生，你要是肯跟我合作
you wouldn't be in this mess.
就不搞到F在@NG人
Someone is blackmailing you,
有人拍了你的同性僬掌砝账髂
so you had him murdered.
所以你就I⑷
Now you know you can't get away with it.
F在你知道跑不掉了，就畏罪自
Did you kill Tse?
是不是你⒘税⒅x的？
- A lawyer. - Lawyer obey the law too.
律…  律照右v法律
You committed murder. A lawyer can't save you.
你⒘巳苏衣就可以身了幔
The deceased was my friend.
死者是我的朋友
I'm speaking to you in a personal capacity.
F在我用私人身份跟你f
I want my lawyer.
我要找我的律
Don't throw a lawyer at me. You killed my friend.
你不要用律砘Ｎ
- I didn't... - You didn't?
我]有⑷恕  ]有⑷耍
Then why won't you co-operate? You say!
]有⑷嗽觞N不跟我合作？你f
I didn't kill.
我]有⑷
If you co-operate, you can avoid a scandal.
如果合作，你的h就不曝光了
How can you face people now.
你怎N去人？
Where's your shitty bugging device. Let's have it.
用尿充的拿出砹
Did you kill Tse?
你f，是不是你⑺腊⒅x的？
- I didn't. - You still deny it.
我]有  你f]有？
No...
f，是不是你？
Will you talk?
你M嘴胡f八道
If you didn't, who did?
那是l⒌模
The one who's blackmailing you.
是不是勒索你的那人⒌模
If not, then you did it.
如果不是，那一定是你⒌
He can't take it anymore, John.
S邦，他已受不了了
Don't deny it. Who is blackmailing you?
你用不著不承J，是l勒索你？
You're really scum.
你有蛸v的
Now none is going to protect you.
F在]有人可以保得你住
Your name will be ruined. Talk!
你身∶裂了，你f
Ching Han! Him!
n政，是他
Come out soon.
快走
Get a doctor.
快c叫t生恚R先生突然有}
Kam, burn up this false stuff.
阿金，了@些假|西
- What is it? - How will I know?
@是什N？  怎N知道
The only way to save yourself is for you to,
R先生，F在唯一救你的方法
tell us who's blackmailing you.
就是告V我
Han secretly had me photographed,
那些照片是n政找人偷拍的
and has been threatening me to help him move cargo with my ships.
他拿硗{我，要我的船替他\
What sort of cargo?
什N？
Cans. But I don't know what's in them.
罐^，不^我不知道e面是什N
How come Tse is involved?
阿x跟@件事有什NPS？
I don't know him.
我根本不JR他，n政f
Han says Tse found the photos by accident,
姓x的在o意中斓揭槐鞠嗖
and he had to be killed.
所以就⑺缈
What sort of cargo is Han moving?
那叫n政的利用R家年的船
Not sure moving what sort of cargo.
不知道\些什N
I'll search in the godown.
我R上去}
"HANG FUNG SHIPPING CO. LTD. STORE NO. 2"
（FaS船沼邢薰司，二}）
Door's open.
T]i
Told you it's open.
告V你T]i？
Bother.
真麻
Shit, telling me to watch these guys.
搞什N咚咚，像我@N秀的警察
Wasting my talents.
我看著@大玻璃
I will be change a gay early or lately.
早晚我成玻璃圈的T
If I go on the streets,
如果我去巡
crime rate would fall.
犯罪率一定很低的
"DISPENSARY"
（配室）
Got it!
有}
Let's move this out.
各位兄弟，兔
- Put the goods onto the truck quickly. - Yes.
s快把\上  是
We'll move it all out tonight.
今天晚上要清}
- Meal's on me. - O. K!
宵夜跳舞我客  好
He looks familiar. Do you know him?
那砘锖妹媸炷阏JR他？
It's the number 1 from the next district.
叫Peter，隔壁局e的老大
Han is really good.
n政也真害
Got our people too.
B我的人也得
- Blonde chick. - Target for emigration.
洋妞  追到可以移民
This is even better, can't emigrate, pick this one.
@也不e，不想移民就追@
Where's my snack?
宵夜呢？
- Catch! - Thank you!
接住  xx
Peanuts, kumquats, apricots, beef jerky and chocolates.
花生、蜜T、牛肉乾、巧克力
- You have to eat it all up. - O. K!
你全部都要吃光  好
- He's my partner, Kam! - Hello!
@是我同事阿金  你好
Clumsy Lun, I see you're not so clumsy now.
不是w的，有一套
Really, is he clumsy?
他M只一套
- Well, enough? - Miss!
怎N樱虿颍  小姐
All the nurses are so pretty.
你t院的o士都很漂亮
Even that blonde nurse just now is pretty.
^去的洋妞也很正c
Blondes! This hospital has only Chinese nurses.
洋妞？我t院]有外人o士
- The salt water bottle. - Shit!
c滴  糟了
Where are you going?
你要去哪e？
Sorry!
Σ黄
- What is it? - Look after Mr. Ho!
什N事？  看著他
Lun, what is it?
阿，怎N了？
Hurry and get out.
艾_，快走
- Get her out. - Yes, Sir!
小黑，把他拖出去  是
What's happened?
什N事？
Careful. Take Ho to the 13/F. Quick!
小心c，快把R先生送到十三牵快
Hold it!
站住
- Something is wrong upstairs. - Shit!
上面出事了，快走  糟了
Auntie...
阿姨…
Kam, come with me.
阿金，跟我
Hurry up!
快
Hurry! Get up!
快c…快上去
Kam, turn off the mains.
阿金，把源P掉
Coming down, hurry.
下砹耍快c
Damn you!
你娘的
Wong, are you really?
S警官，是不是你？
Yes, have you seen him?
是，你有]有看什N
No.
]有
Oh, I seen him.
看他了
Wong!
S警官
What are you doing here, go down.
你上质颤N？下去
Kam, careful down below.
阿金，注意下面
What are you doing below.
阿金，你在上面质颤N？
I hit the safety switch by mistake.
我碰到安全o了
Shit!
你娘的
That guy's hanging.
S警官，他被吊起砹
Help me! I can't take it, save me!
痛死我了，受不了了
I can see him, John!
S邦，我看他了
Is he near to you now?
他是不是在你附近？
Yes, I'll get him.
在我附近，我Ω端
Help!
救命
It's dangerous, he's got a grenade.
阿翁，危U，他有手榴，s快W_
Oh Shit!
什N咚咚
Get Doctor Chang!
快c叫t恚快c
Mind the way, excuse me!
拿血{出恚快c，一下…
Oxygen, we need oxygen.
氧狻快c…一…
Let's help him, alright?
你s快退忙，好幔
Hurry, why blood won't come?
快c，血{怎N]恚
- Excuse me! - Blood... hurry up!
一…  血{…快一c
Come here, help me, hurry up!
^恚兔σ幌拢快c
Hold the salt water bottle, hurry up!
拿瓶}水恚快c
We've got Ho's statement.
我已拿到R家年的口供
Why can't we go and get Han now?
槭颤N不可以抓他呢？
Ho is dead.
那R家年已死了
You go and alert Han now,
你F在去幽姓n的
he'll sue you like hell, idiot!
f不定反被他告，笨蛋
That's true. Last year a guy cheated so much money from the banks,
@也Γ去年有姓的砘
but he was judged not guilty.
Y果法庭居然判他o罪
It's a mess anyway.
就是，搞什N咚咚
What is it? All your fathers died?
致铮你都家e死人了
This case is not over yet.
案子]完呢
Look at this.
看看@是什N|西？
Powdered milk.
奶粉
That's right, what's wrong?
Γ奶粉，有什N不Γ
If so many can get killed over powdered milk,
榱诉@些奶粉，要死那N多人
women wouldn't dare have children.
l敢生孩子？
Let's take it for tests.
我先拿去化
We have an informer in the police.
莉，我警方有燃
You must help us find out what this stuff is.
所以一定要你臀化一下
What are these? Plant seeds.
@是什N？N子幔
I'll let you know.
等化出恚我M快告V你
It's urgent but you be careful.
我m然急，可是你也要小心c
Nobody must know about it.
@整事情^Σ荒茏e人知道
I'll conduct the tests when none is around.
我等]人的r候再化，放心吧
Call me when you have the results.
有Y果就o我
I'll wait for your call.
我等你消息，走
John.
S邦
Let's go. It's a family affair.
走了，家庭m
Wait!
等我一下
This is your birthday gift to me.
@是你送我的生日Y物
Do you want it back?
要不要拿回去？
I'll call you with the results.
有了Y果，我立刻通知你的
Just take care.
你自己要小心c
I will.
我的
I hope I can help you break the case.
我希望能湍闫瓢
He's back, quiet.
他回砹耍不要再f了
These guys have really got guts.
@群s碎，一定吃了熊心豹
Following us again!
後面有人跟我
What do we do?
搞什N咚咚，F在怎Nk？
Calm down, they won't get away.
沉著c，@次一也跑不掉
Hawk calling H.Q., I'm P.C. Chan.
老呼叫部，我是警官
According to the information, we discovered the drug dealer.
根情螅我已lF毒的行
We must stick an eye on him, over.
我一定盯住他的，Over
This is Inspector Wong.
呼叫部，我是SS邦
I'm going past Sheung Wan Street.
我的位置行上h街
One light brown 4-door sedan,
lF一v\咖啡色四T房
registration B.T. 6041.
牌aBT6041
4 suspects in the car.
e有四人，形E可疑
We are proceeding to Wing Lok Street.
我F在正朝永方址较蛐旭
Keep an eye on them, over!
我一定O他，Over
We've got to catch them today.
今天一定要抓住他
Here they come.
他砹耍下
I've never had a gun fight yet.
S警官，我]有疬^
Shut the door and watch the fun.
P上T看狒[好了
Looks like they're armed.
S警官，那些咚咚有
They're armed.
e面的人有砘
Get some help.
管不了那N多了，快通知部
Those inside do not move. We are C.I.D.
e面的人不要樱我是刑警
We're C.I.D. Too. Why are you following us?
我也是刑警，槭颤N要跟我？
We'll shoot if you don't come out.
我怎N知道你是不是刑警
Shit, whoever shoots first gets it.
@下糗了，l先_就l倒霉
Get down!
蹲下…
Put your I.D. Away.
把C件戴好
They are getting out their guns.
他拔了
Kam, Ong, don't shoot. Someone is playing a bad joke on us.
阿金、阿翁，不要_，都是自己人
Kam, Ong!
阿金、阿翁
Really C.I.D.'s.
真的是警察
How are you?
你怎N樱
- A gun fight! - This serious?
蔷官，  穑@N乐兀
Someone was lying in wait for us.
蔷官，有人O我
- Attack the police? Seal the place! - Yes, sir!
敢打警察？封iF  是
Looks like guys from the next district.
蔷官，好像是自己人
Bad luck for them, barging in on us like this.
自己人？
You jerks come up with something new each day.
@些s碎真有一套
Don't let news of this get out.
@件事情千f不能鞒鋈
Or it will make the top 10 charts.
否t一定列入世界十大^l新
Our crime unit says someone is following them,
我的刑事M通知部f是
someone gave us a tip-off to follow your guys, Sir!
是我的人o我情
- Tell them all to come out. Now. - Yes, Sir!
叫他全部L出恚Now  是
All of you inside come out.
e面的人全部L出
This is Ng. Don't come out.
我是蔷官，我的人不要出
How can you guarantee your guys won't attack my guys.
你怎N保C你的人不偷u我的人？
If my guys were to shoot, your guys can't come out.
如果我的人要_火，你的人出得
I guarantee their safety.
我保C他安全
O.K.
你叫吧
I'm Law from Central.
我是中h^_警官
Our guys come out.
所有的人都o我出
Who started the shooting?
你究竟是l先_的？
I'll put this in my report, you just wait.
我一定ze你的，走著瞧
I fired the first shot.
我先_
People like you ruin the police's image.
我警察的形象
Do you think that Peter arranged this.
今晚@件事
Isn't that Ching Han?
那不是n政幔
Inspector Wong, pleased to meet you.
SS邦督察，久仰了
How are you?
你好幔
I hear your gang is very thorough, good!
f你做起事砗氐椎
Hong Kong has only 10 years left, not much time.
氐缀茫香港只剩下十年、八年了
How can we make a living if we are not thorough.
如果不氐自觞N活呢？
You know we are investigating you.
我正在查你
You have your hands on my shoulders, wanna deal?
你F在勾肩搭背的是不是想要判？
I don't know about deals.
我是生意人，有什N好判呢？
I knew you'd come looking for me.
我知道你早晚碚椅
That's why I've come voluntarily.
所以我主砀你合作
Go ahead, ask. I'll try my best to answer.
你管吧，我的答覆你M意的
The answers you can give are probably not good enough.
你的答覆，很y我M意
No hurry, I'll be looking for you.
你不用急，我一定找你的
Don't get a ticket for Seattle when the time comes.
到r候你不要IwC票去西雅D就好
You dropped something.
警官，你掉了包|西
Take it home and look it over.
拿回去慢慢看吧
I don't know which beggar threw that dirty money away.
@缺德X不缘檬悄要的掉了
Tell him to go eat shit.
叫它去吃屎吧
Did you see that face!
你有]有看到n政那副德性？
Watching us throw his money away.
看著我把他的X跟⒓X一拥娜
- What fun! - Fun, eh!
好^a  好^a呢？
My heart broke when I saw that money go.
我看到那些X被G到海e我心痛的
You can't suspend me now.
署L
I'm nearly there.
@案子我已要找到索了
Let me go on.
你我查下去，你想
How can there be suddenly $300,000 in my bank?
我y行纛^怎N突然多出了三十f
Someone is setting me up.
@分明是有人要整我
Sorry, I.C.A.C. Is after you.
]k法，@是污M要{查你
Even then, I don't need to be suspended.
就算是要{查我，也不用停我的
When will we get enough evidence to get Han?
什Nr候才能查到C捉那姓n的
You talk to the I.C.A.C.
有什N你去跟污Mf好了
Just give me one more month.
再o我一月的rg
Otherwise all my work goes down the drain.
否t我M@N多的功夫，都白M了
Superintendent, Wong...
署L，S警官…
Anymore from you, you get an investigation too.
再吵，B你也停
Lun, don't mess about. I'll fix the boss.
阿，不要y恚我Ω端
Ho was murdered at the hospital.
R家年在t院e被人家⒘
This case is not finished yet.
你好
You'll be busy at the Courts all the time.
@件案子光跑法院就蚰闩艿牧
Don't go on investigating this month.
@月你不必查案
I've got to make a call.
署L，我去回
Lun, Maggie called.
阿，莉在Call我
- Go and see what it is. - OK.
麻┠闾嫖一  好
Hello, Maggie, Lun here.
莉，我是
I've got it, it's cocaine seeds.
阿，我已出砹
After refinement, it becomes heroin.
提^之後就是古柯z了
I'll tell Inspector Wong!
毒品？我R上通知S警官
One and half minutes left.
有一分半
Throw it out the window.
快G出去
No, there are pedestrians.
不行，街上有好多人
- There's building site there. - Excuse me!
那有K空地  快
- Move over! - Excuse...
_  _了
This way! Hurry up!
@…快c
Excuse...
_了
- That's way! Hurry up! - What do you do?
在那e…快一c  你致铮
Calling H. Q!
呼叫部…
Move off!
_了
I'll shoot if you don't stop.
再跑我就_了
What is it?
什N咚咚？
Hurry up!
快c
I'm C.I. D!
我是刑警
Move off!
_
Don't run... l'll shoot.
e跑…再跑我_了
You're idiot!
你是i？
Are you O.K. Kam?
你怎N樱
You're right, I'm slow.
你f得很Γ我是反比^慢
To let that old soldier shoot me, shit on shit.
要不然，也不被那菜B打一
You...
你…
My mother is really stubborn.
我脾獠缓
She mustn't know I'm shot.
不要跟她v我受
Kam...
阿金…
Do you know where my son Kam is?
小姐，我鹤影⒔鹚住滋床？
The cop with the bad temper?
你是f那脾夂牡木察是不是？
Right, where is he?
是…他住滋床？
- In bed number 52. - Thank you! Kam!
他在五十二床  xx，阿金…
Oh Shit!
什N咚咚了
- Who shall I say it's from? - Waipong Wong?
先生，下款什N？  SS邦
- How much? - Waipong Wong, $200.
多少X？  砂K，xx
Attention! Start!
注意，暴形_始
John! You have to go to Court tomorrow.
S邦，你明天要出庭？
I'm going back to K.L. Tomorrow.
我明天要回吉隆坡了
Your boss reported on me to my boss.
你上司打蟾娼o我部
H.Q. Wants me back.
部要立刻s回去蟮
Can't send you off.
我明天要出庭，]rg送你
- Take care! - I will!
你保重  我的
Sorry! Wong!
Σ黄穑S警官
I don't know whether it's the right time to resign.
我不知道F在fo呈是不是r候？
My mother is afraid I'll get killed.
可是我她怕得要死
She needs me to take care of her.
她怕]有鹤咏o她送K
Don't worry, I'll fix it.
好，我湍戕k
If you need help, anytime.
以後有事需要我，Sr找我
"The Supreme Court"
（最高法院）
Do you have any comments on this investigation?
S警官，@次你被{查有什N意？
Sorry, no comments.
]意
Mr. Han!
n先生
How come you're involved in this?
@一件案子怎N可娴侥隳兀
Actually decent businessmen like me,
其我生意人
hate law keepers who are corrupt. Sorry!
最那些谭ㄕ呤蘸阱X了，Σ黄
I never knew we'd see one another in Court.
想不到我真的在法庭面了
But you're not after me, I'm after you.
不^@次不是你查我，是我查你
Frankly, this is your chance to go straight.
老f，你@次能螂x_黑暗的警界
I feel sorry for you too.
我真替你c幸
I've always doubted Hong Kong's law,
其我ο愀鄣姆律多少有c岩
but a lot of people are wasting good time,
不^F在很多人浪M不少rg
nowadays studying basic law, actually there is no law.
在@研究什N法，其根本就是o法
Small matter.
小事情
Spend a few years inside. Start again.
M去坐啄昀纬碛质且l好h
Don't worry. Nothing will happen.
放心吧，不有事的
Any problems, call me.
有什N搞不定的，管碚椅液昧
You bastard.
你@混蛋
- Don't fight! - Let him go!
阿…不要打  你放_他
- Bastard! - Don't fight!
你@混蛋  不要打
Excuse me! Don't fight!
_…不要打了
Let me go, I'll beat him to death.
放_我，我打死他，放_我
Don't bother, kid. You need some vitamin pills.
小鬼，拿去I汽水喝吧
Let's go!
_
Don't you leave.
你@混蛋，不要跑
- There are reporters here. - Let me go!
阿，@e很多者  放_我
- Don't fail for it! - I can't live with it.
不要中  我不服猓放_我…
If this is what a cop's life is, I quit.
@N警察我不至
- Lun! - Lun. Kwok Keung Lun!
阿  阿，
Lun. Kwok Keung Lun!
阿，
- Where are you off to? - Come on!
你要去哪e？  不要跟著我
Lun...
阿…
$15!
十五K
That's right. Just let it blow over.
α耍年p人，吵完了架就]事了
Love forever!
百年好合
- $58. - Miss! Give me a lighter.
五十八  小姐，o我打火C
- O. K! - $15.
好的  十五K
What is it?
到底什N事？
Notify Inspector Wong and Kam.
快去通知S警官跟阿金
Tell them to wait, I've got a new clue.
叫他等我消息，我有新索，快
Let's go!
_
At least you have to tell me where to go.
就算_，你也要告V我到哪e去
I'm C.I.D. Follow that Rolls Royce.
我是刑警，跟著前面那部
After some robbers?
捉\？
Where did you go?
你要去哪e？
Don't ask me to do dangerous things.
危U的事不要找我
You take the car, I'll get it back from police station.
子你拿去好了，我去警局拿回的
You bungled the job, the cargo nearly didn't go out.
你k事太差帕
It will be even more inconvenient.
以後更不方便了
The police are watching us.
警方已注意到了
Our transport network in S.E. Asia,
我在|南安排很多的\W
has been completely destroyed by you.
F在一下子全o你搞砸了
Ching Han, you are a man of resources,
n政，你不是很有k法幔
now there's a problem, what then?
F在出了}，看你怎咏Q？
Mr. Molotov, Hong Kong will be handed over soon,
雪洛托夫先生，香港再啄昃偷骄牌
many are waiting to emigrate.
F在很多的人都等待著移民
They need money.
他需要X
I agree with you.
我同意你的看法
This is the time to grab money.
所以要把握rC埔还P
As long as we pay the price,
只要我付得起X
not to mention drugs,
不要f是\毒品
you can ship the entire Hong Kong to your country.
整香港\到你老家去也行
This list are high government officials.
那份名紊厦娑际钦府的重要人物
Yes, we spent some money,
m然是花cX
but compared to our profits,
但是比起砦回收的利
this investment is peanuts.
@一次的投Y只能算是零^小XT了
Traveler Chat Fu Ong, who took flight 071 to Malaysia,
搭乘R砦071次班C旅客
please contact the airport enquiry center.
翁振富先生R上跟C鲈Bj
You're right. Everybody looks to money now.
你f得ΓF在全世界都是向X看
Selling drugs and capitalism together is the best way.
我把毒品和Y本主x
Let's drink to 1997.
恚橐痪啪牌咔杯
- Cheers! - To greater success.
好，大家乾杯  合作成功
Mr. Han, that rookie has followed us here.
n先生，那菜B跟上砹
Freeze!
不要
Trying to scare somebody?
你质颤N，想死我？
- Have you called Inspector Wong! - He'll be here soon.
通知S警官]有？  他快到了
I've recorded Han's meeting.
我偷到n政跟e人_的热
He's moving drugs for the Russians.
原硭投人\毒品
Han's nailed this time.
@一次n政死定了
Lun!
阿
It's that guy.
是那人
Can't call out.
打不通了
Go through that window.
艾_，拇翱谔映鋈
Jump down, quick.
快跳下去，快
And give the tape to Inspector Wong!
把音Ы唤oS警官
How come your face can be cut by a blade?
怎N？你的用刀也可以割_的
I thought it was made of steel.
我以槟闶氰F做的
I despise stupid people like you.
我最的就是你@N人
You do not treasure your life.
不巯ё约旱纳命
You go all the way each time,
硬泳娃彰
with no ulterior motive, no gains.
]有目的又]有好
I don't know for what.
也不知道槭颤N？
I thought stubborn people like you have already become extinct.
我以橄衲氵@N不Rr盏娜
Mr. Han, we found the tape.
n先生，我找到了音Я
Other than the kid,
除了@小子
others must know our secret too.
我想有其他人知道我的秘密
Pity, bad enough for you.
可惜，你自己惹上身
Why did you get others involved?
F在要B累e人，那有什N意思呢
You want a quick death, tell me who's heard this tape before.
如果你想死得舒服一c就老告V我
The janitor is dead.
管理T死了
Lun!
阿
Don't, Lun!
阿，不要了
- Let me go! - Don't go over there.
放_我…  S警官，你不要^去了
- Lun... - Sir.
阿…  S警官
Lun!
阿
Let's go!
走
Hide.
趴下
Cari mati!
他的
Let's go!
走
That's way!
在那
Kam...
阿金…
Hurry!
快走
I'll smash you to death.
撞死你@王八蛋
Don't release the pedal.
按著油T
Jump, we're crashing.
快撞上了，跳
- Are you O. K? - No problem!
你]事吧？  ]事
You bastard, go to hell!
你@混蛋，去死…
Few years later will be 1997.
香港再啄昃偷骄牌
Many people are waiting for immigration.
F在很多的人都等待著移民
They need money.
他需要X
I agree with you.
我同意你的看法
We should take this time and earn some money.
所以要把握rC狠埔还P
As long as we can pay for it,
只要我付得起X
not only smuggling drug,
不要f是\毒品
I can smuggle everything in Hong Kong to your place.
整香港\到你老家去也行
People in the list are important people in the government.
那份名紊厦娑际钦府的重要人物
We never found out who's on Han's list.
我始K不知到n政名紊嫌心切┤
But the drugs leaving Hong Kong were found by the Marine Police.
不^部分的毒品已被水警查@了
At least your efforts were not wasted.
起a你的辛苦]有白M
The doctor says my stitches will be removed next month.
S警官，t生f我下月就可以拆
I want to apply to be with you.
我想再申回砀你
I thought you wanted to quit.
你不是不想警察了幔
On second thoughts,
我想^了
in this world, it would be safer to carry a gun.
@世界上是拿比^安全一c
Excuse me, which one is Inspector Wong?
…哪一位是SS邦督察？
I've been transferred from the Western District.
我是奈^{砀他W的
Number 1003, Chuchia Butt!
1003楚嘉
Don't know where he's...
不知道他是不是在@警局服铡
I am Waipong Wong!
我就是SS邦
We'll talk about it back in the station.
有事回局e再f，上吧
Yes, Sir!
是，警官
This car, don't you want your own car?
上我的？你自己不要了？
Working with this long-haired weirdo, shit!
什N咚咚，要跟大R猴一M
Wait me!
等等我…